Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
- Part I. Audiovisual material
  - Phonodiscs
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0363; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0364; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0365; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0366; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0367; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0368; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 165)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0369; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0370; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0371; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0372; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0373; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0374; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0375; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0376; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0377; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0378; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - Silent Night; O, Little Town of Bethlehem, 1949; lewis_f_jr_0379; produced by United States Recording Co.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - SoundScriber level test, lewis_f_jr_0409; SoundScriber disc found in the SoundScriber machine No. 1. This is a level test of the machine.; VinylDisc (Box 166)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0397; produced by National Recording Studios, Inc.; Aluminum Record (Box 166)
- Part II. Correspondence
  See also Part I, Correspondence.
  - Incoming
    - A-B, 1950-1953 (Box 168)
    - C, 1950-1953 (Box 168)
    - D, 1950-1953 (Box 168)
    - E, 1951-1953 (Box 168)
    - F, 1949-1964 (Box 168)
    - G, 1950-1952 (Box 169)
    - H, 1950-1952 (Box 169)
    - I-K, 1950-1952 (Box 169)
    - L, 1950-1953; undated (Box 169)
    - M, 1949-1953 (Box 169)
    - N-P, 1949-1953 (Box 170)
    - Q-R, 1950-1953 (Box 170)
    - S, 1950-1953 (Box 170)
    - T-V, 1950-1953 (Box 170)
    - W, 1950-1953 (Box 170)
    - Y-Z; no name, 1951-1952; undated (Box 170)
  - Outgoing
    - Outgoing, 1950-1953; 1964; 4 folders (Box 171)
      Date ranges: 1951 Jan 5-Dec 18; 1952 Jan 7-Dec 4; 1953 Jan 3-Aug 20; 1964 Apr 6-13
    - Outgoing, undated (Box 171)
  - Fan mail, chronological
    - Fan mail, 1950-1952; 1956,; 1960-1963 Sep 19; 11 folders (Box 172)
    - Fan mail, 1963 Sep 20-Nov 30; 5 folders (Box 173)
    - Fan mail, 1963, no date (Box 173)
    - Fan mail, 1963 Dec (Box 174)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Jan-Feb 16 (Box 174)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Feb 17-Mar 19 (Box 175)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Mar 20-Apr 25 (Box 176)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Apr 26-Jun 16 (Box 177)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Jun 17-Jul 26 (Box 178)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Jul 27-Aug 6 (Box 179)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Aug 7-Sep 15 (Box 180)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Sep 16, 30; Oct 1-21; 2 folders (Box 181)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Oct 26-Nov 15 (Box 182)
    - Fan mail, 1964 Nov 16-Dec 31; undated (Box 183)
    - Fan mail, 1964, no date (Box 184)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Jan 2-Feb 18 (Box 184)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Feb 19-25 (Box 185)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Feb 25-28 (Box 186)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Apr 3-5 (Box 187)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Apr 5-8 (Box 188)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Apr 9-12 (Box 189)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Apr 13-Jul 31 (Box 190)
    - Fan mail [box is out of order], 1965 Mar 1-29 (Box 191)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Aug 2-30 (Box 191)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Mar 30-Apr 1 (Box 192)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Apr 1-2 (Box 193)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Apr 2 (Box 194)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Apr 2 (Box 195)
    - Fan mail, 1965 Sep 1-Dec 31 (Box 196)
    - Fan mail, 1965, no date; 2 folders (Box 196)
    - Fan mail, 1966 Jan 1-Jun 28; 4 folders (Box 197)
    - Fan mail, 1966, no date (Box 197)
    - Fan mail, undated; 2 folders (Box 198)
- Part II. Subject files
  - Analysis of Federal Grants, 1965 (Box 199)
  - Broadcasts, 1953; 10 folders (Box 199)
    Jan 28; Feb 9; Mar 2-4; Mar 16-30; Apr 14-15; Jun 22; Jul 4; Sep 10-30; Oct 21-30; Nov 9-24
  - Broadcasts, 1954; 4 folders (Box 199)
    Dates: Jan 12; Jul 26-27; Aug 2-12; Nov 24-25
  - Broadcasts, 1955; 2 folders (Box 199)
    Dates: Nov 15-29; Dec 1-8
  - Broadcasts, 1956; 3 folders (Box 199)
    Dates: Jan 26; Feb 2; May 11-23
  - Broadcasts, 1957; 4 folders (Box 199)
    Dates: Aug 22-28; Oct 31; Nov 12-15; Dec 16-27
  - Broadcasts, 1958; 6 folders (Box 199)
    Dates: Jan 6-30; Feb 4-27; Mar 5-14; Mar 17-31; Apr 1-18; May 7-8
  - Broadcasts, undated (Box 199)
  - Cards, 1966 (Box 199)
  - Deposit ticket, undated (Box 199)
  - Editorials by others, 1953 Nov 11-1966 Apr 7; undated; 2 folders (Box 199)
  - Essays, A-W, 1963-1965 (Box 200)
  - Hearings, C-J, 1965 (Box 200)
  - Honorary appointment, 1963 (Box 200)
  - Information Kit "Miller", 1964 (Box 200)
  - Meeting announcements and invitations, 1962-1966; undated; 3 folders (Box 200)
  - Music compositions, 1963 (Box 200)
  - Office memos, 1960-1966; undated; 5 folders (Box 200)
  - Order forms, 1966 (Box 200)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 200)
  - Polls, 1964 (Box 200)
  - Posters, 1964-1966 (Box 200)
  - Railroad graft, 1966 (Box 200)
  - Rally stamps, 1966 (Box 200)
  - Reports, A-S, 1963-1966 (Box 200)
  - Reprints, 1938-1966 (Box 201)
  - Speeches, 1951-1966 (Box 201)
  - Summary, 1965 (Box 201)
  - Teletypes, Introduction, #7-191, undated; 2 folders (Box 201)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1954; 2 folders (Box 202)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1955; 3 folders (Box 202)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1957 Feb 1-1958 Apr 16 (Box 202)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1959; 4 folders (Box 202)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1960; 4 folders (Box 202)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1961; 3 folders (Box 202)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1962 Jan 2-1963 Jan 31 (Box 203)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1963 Feb-Dec; 6 folders (Box 203)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1964; 6 folders (Box 203)
  - Washington Report Rep., 1965 Aug 2-1966 Mar 11 (Box 203)
- Part II. Manuscripts
  See also Part I, Other productions.
  - Top of the News
    - Stencils of Lewis' Broadcasts on Radio Free Europe (Box 204)
    - Miscellaneous radio broadcasts, May 1949-Jun 1959 (Box 204)
    - Miscellaneous radio broadcasts, Mar 15-Dec 14, 1950 (Box 204)
    - Excerpts (photostats), Nov 5, 1957-Dec 31, 1960 (Box 204)
    - Excerpts, Feb 10-Jun 6, 1958; 1 original typescript, 1 mimeograph (Box 204)
    - Excerpts, Oct 29-31, 1962 (Box 204)
    - Indexes to "Top of the News", 1952-1965 (Box 205)
  - Washington Report
    - Washington Report, 1951 Jan 30 (Box 206)
    - Washington Report, 1953; 2 folders (Box 206)
      Dates: Oct 12-30; Nov 2-30
    - Washington Report, 1954; 12 folders (Box 206)
      Dates: Jan 1-29; Feb 1-25; Mar 3-31; Apr 1-30; May 3-31; Jun 1-30; Jul 1-22; Aug 2-31; Sep 1-30; Oct 1-29; Nov 1-30; Dec 2-30
    - Washington Report, 1955; 12 folders (Box 207)
      Dates: Jan 3-31; Feb 2-28; Mar 1-31; Apr 1-29; May 2-30; Jun 2-30; Jul 1-29; Aug 1-31; Sep 1-30; Oct 3-31; Nov 1-30; Dec 1-30
    - Washington Report, 1957 (Box 207)
      Dates: May, Dec
    - Washington Report, 1959; 10 folders (Box 208)
      Dates: Jan 3-31; Feb 2-26; Mar 2-30; Apr 7-May 24; Jun 4-Jul 29; Aug 3-31; Sep 1-30; Oct 5-30; Nov 3-30; Dec 1-31
    - Washington Report, 1960; 12 folders (Box 208)
      Dates: Jan 1-20; Feb 2-29; Mar 1-28; Apr 5-20; May 2-31; Jun 1-30; Jul 1-26; Aug 11-30; Sep 2-29; Oct 3-31; Nov 1-19; Dec 6-30
    - Washington Report, 1961; 12 folders (Box 209)
      Dates: Jan 1-31; Feb 1-27; Mar 2-31; Apr 3-18; May 1-30; Jun 5-26; Jul 4-31; Aug 1-28; Sep 11-Oct 31; Nov 1-29; Dec 1-29
    - Washington Report, 1962; 12 foldes (Box 210)
      Dates: Jan 2-31; Feb 1-28; Mar 1-30; Apr 2-27; May 1-31; Jun 1-29; Jul 4-31; Aug 1-31; Sep 3-29; Oct 1-31; Nov 2-30; Dec 3-31
    - Washington Report, 1963; 12 folders (Box 211)
      Dates: Jan 1-31; Feb 1-28; Mar 1-29; Apr 1-30; May 1-31; Jun 4-28; Jul 1-31; Aug 1-30; Sep 1-28; Oct 1-17; Nov 4-29; Dec 7-30
    - Washington Report, 1964; 12 folders (Box 212)
      Dates: Jan 13-31; Feb 4-28; Mar 2-30; Apr 1-30; May 1-31; Jun 1-30; Jul 3-30; Aug 4-19; Sep 2-31; Oct 2-30; Nov 2-30; Dec 3-30
- Part II. Press releases and newsletters
  - A, 1961-1966; 3 folders (Box 213)
  - B, 1964-1966 (Box 213)
  - B, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 214)
  - C, 1963-1966; 2 folders (Box 214)
  - C, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 215)
  - C, 1964-1966 (Box 216)
  - Congressional, 1963-1966; 3 folders (Box 216)
  - Congressional, 1964-1966 (Box 217)
  - C, 1962-1966; 3 folders (Box 217)
  - C, 1962-1966; 4 folders (Box 218)
  - C, 1964-1966 (Box 219)
  - D, 1964-1966 (Box 219)
  - E-F, 1964-1966 (Box 219)
  - G-H, 1964-1966 (Box 219)
  - I, 1950-1966 (Box 220)
  - J-M, 1964-1966 (Box 220)
  - N, 1964-1966 (Box 220)
  - N, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 221)
  - O-Q, 1964-1966 (Box 221)
  - R, 1964-1966 (Box 221)
  - R, 1963-1966; 4 folders (Box 222)
  - R, 1964; 2 folders (Box 223)
  - S-T, 1964-1966 (Box 223)
  - U, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 224)
  - U, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 225)
  - U, 1963-1966; 4 folders (Box 226)
  - U, 1963-1966 (Box 227)
  - USD-Z, 1964-1966 (Box 227)
  - Fragments (Box 227)
- Part II. Reference files
  See also Part I, Reference files.
  - American Bar Association, 1957-1959; undated (Box 228)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1955-1961 (Box 228)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1955-1959; undated (Box 228)
  - Arkansas Tax Case, 1952; undated (Box 228)
  - Arkansas Tax Case, 1952; undated (Box 228)
  - Blood Bank Foundation, Inc. of Nashville, Tenn., 1951-1952; undated; 2 folders (Box 228)
  - Caldwell, John C., 1950-1951 (Box 228)
  - California Intelligence Bureau, 1958 (Box 228)
  - Condon, Dr. Edward U., 1948 (Box 228)
  - Education (General), 1942; 1951-1959,; undated; 3 folders (Box 228)
  - Education (General): The White House Conference, 1955-1958; undated (Box 228)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1956-1959; undated (Box 229)
  - Emerson, Thomas I, 1943-1952; undated (Box 229)
  - Fabianism of John Kennedy (Box 229)
  - Ford Foundation, 1955 (Box 229)
  - Free Europe Committee (Free Europe Press), 1954 (Box 229)
  - Freistadt, Han, 1949 (Box 229)
  - General Agreement on Tariffs & Trade (Gatt), 1955-1962; undated; 4 folders (Box 229)
  - Germany, 1961 (Box 229)
  - Graham, Dr. Frank Porter, 1948-1949 (Box 229)
  - Giraud, Chester, 1949 (Box 229)
  - Harris, Rev. Frederick Brown, 1953 (Box 229)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee [HUAC], 1961; undated (Box 229)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1935-1960; undated; 4 folders (Box 230)
  - Jessup, Dr. Philip C., 1949-1951; undated (Box 230)
  - Johnson, Adelaide, 1909-1952 (Box 230)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1954 (Box 230)
  - Lamon, Corliss and Margaret, 1958; undated (Box 230)
  - Laos, 1959-1961 (Box 230)
  - Lattimore, Owen, 1954-1957; undated (Box 230)
  - Leagues of Women Voters, 1954-1962; undated; 3 folders (Box 230)
  - Little Rock, Arkansas (U.S. Court of Appeals), 1957; 1963 (Box 230)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1951; 1957,; undated (Box 231)
  - McCarthy, Joseph
    - [General], 1954-1955; undated; 2 folders (Box 231)
    - Report on Pres. (Box 231)
    - [General], 1953-1958; undated (Box 231)
  - Menshikov, Mikhail, 1958; undated (Box 231)
  - Moise, Sen. Wayne, 1934-1959 (Box 231)
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1955-1961 (Box 231)
  - "Muzzling of the Military", Aug-Dec 1960-1961; 2 folders (Box 231)
  - NAACP [National Association for the Advancement of Colored People], 1955-1958; undated (Box 231)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1956-1960; undated; 2 folders (Box 231)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1952-1962; undated (Box 231)
  - Peace Corps, 1961; undated (Box 231)
  - Pearson, Drew, 1958 (Box 231)
  - People
    - Lardner-Lerner (Box 232)
    - Lewis-Luce (Box 232)
    - Macleish-Moore (Box 232)
    - Morris-Myer (Box 232)
    - Nathan-Nuguist (Box 232)
    - O'Conner-Overstreet (Box 232)
    - Paine-Powell (Box 232)
    - Redfield-Rosenbergs (Box 232)
    - Salpeter-Smith (Box 232)
    - Sobell-Symengton (Box 232)
    - Taylor-Trumbo (Box 232)
    - U Nu-Uphaus (Box 232)
    - Van Doren-Vincent (Box 232)
    - Warne-Wyzanski (Box 232)
  - Philippines, 1959; undated (Box 232)
  - Political party platforms, 1956 (Box 232)
  - Political polls, 1951-1959; undated (Box 232)
  - Portugal, 1962 (Box 232)
  - Pugwash Conference, 1957-1958; undated; international anti-war/disarmament organization, founded 1957 by Joseph Rotblat and Bertrand Russell in Pugwash, Nova Scotia (Box 232)
  - Radio Free Europe, 1954-1962; undated (Box 233)
  - Republican Party, 1961-1962; undated (Box 233)
  - Reuther, Walter, 1955-1958; undated (Box 233)
  - Rockefeller Report on U.S. International Economic Policy, 1958 (Box 233)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1946-1954; undated (Box 233)
  - Rosenberg, Anna, 1950-1951 (Box 233)
  - Russia, 1928; 1954-1963,; undated; 3 folders (Box 233)
  - Security (Risks), 1955-1961 (Box 233)
  - Service, John Stewart, 1949-1957 (Box 233)
  - Shelton, Turner, 1958-1959; undated (Box 233)
  - Smart, Anne, 1954-1961; 2 folders (Box 233)
  - Seattle Law Suit (of Richard Atwood), 1950-1951 (Box 233)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K., 1950-1954 (Box 233)
  - Spain (the Spanish Story), 1949 (Box 234)
  - Stassen, Harold, 1956-1959; undated (Box 234)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1951-1952 (Box 234)
  - Southern Conference Education Fund, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 234)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1955-1957 (Box 234)
  - Strauss, Lewis, 1958-1959; undated; 3 folders (Box 234)
  - Steibert, Theodore C., 1948 (Box 234)
  - Students, 1952-1962 (Box 234)
  - Tydings, Millard, 1930-1946; 1950-1951,; undated; 4 folders (Box 234)
  - United Nations, 1949-1962; undated; 2 folders (Box 235)
  - United States Foreign Policy, miscellaneous (Box 235)
  - Wallace, Henry, 1943-1946; undated (Box 235)
  - Wirin, A.L., 1957-1959 (Box 235)
  - World Council of Churches, 1961; undated (Box 235)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1961-1962 (Box 235)
  - Yugoslavia, 1954-1963 (Box 235)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1962; undated (Box 235)
- Part II. Published material
  - Newspapers
    - Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 236)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 236)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 236)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 236)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 236)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 237)
    - Clippings about Lewis (Box 237)
      Material is unfoldered.
    - Clippings by and about others (Box 237)
  - Magazines
    - A-C (Box 238)
    - D-N (Box 239)
    - O-W (Box 240)
  - Brochures
    - Miscellaneous, A-R (Box 241)
  - Clippings
    - By Lewis (Box 242)
    - About Lewis (Box 242)
    - By and about others, 2 folders (Box 242)
    - By and about others, 2 folders (Box 243)
  - Flyers
    - A-P, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 243)
    - R-Y, 1964-1966 (Box 244)
  - Congressional Record
    See also Part II, Congressional Record.
    - Congressional Record, Sep 18, 1961-Dec 4, 1963 (Box 244)
    - Congressional Record, Jan 15-Oct 3, 1964 (Box 244)
    - Congressional Record, Mar 8, 1965-Jun 1, 1966 (Box 244)
  - Pamphlets
    - Miscellaneous, A-X, 3 folders (Box 244)
  - Weekly newsletters
    - "Exclusive", 1963 Jan 9-Dec 31 (Box 245)
    - "Exclusive", 1964 Jan 8-Dec 30; 3 folders (Box 245)
    - "Exclusive", 1965 Apr 14-Dec 22; 2 folders (Box 245)
    - Top of the News, Volume 1 no. 1 to Volume 3, no. 26, 6 Jul 1959-30 Jun 1961 (Box 246)
      Issues of this newsletter have also been cataloged; please refer to to locate a complete listing of issues.
    - Top of the News, Volume 3, no. 27 to Volume 5, no. 26; Index, 3 Jul 1961-28 Jun 1963 (Box 247)
    - Top of the News, Volume 5, no. 27 to Volume 6, no. 52; Index, 1 Jul 1963-25 Dec 1964 (Box 248)
    - Top of the News, Volume 13, no. 1 to Volume 14, no. 40, 1 Jan 1971-26 Oct 1972; includes published transcript from 30 Jan 1962 and typescript from 28 Aug 1962 (Box 249)
- Part II. Duplicates
  - Duplicate broadcasts, 1953; 7 folders (Box 250)
    Dates: Jan 24-Apr 15; Jun 4-23; Jul 22-23; Sep 10-30; Oct 21-23; Oct 26-30; Nov 9-24
  - Duplicate broadcasts, 1954; 3 folders (Box 250)
    Dates: Jan 12; May 31; Jul 26
  - Duplicate broadcasts, 1954; 4 folders (Box 251)
    Dates: Jul 27; Aug 2-12; Nov 22; Nov 24; Nov 25
  - Duplicate broadcasts, 1955; 2 folders (Box 251)
  - Duplicate broadcasts, 1956; 4 folders (Box 251)
    Dates: Feb 2; Apr 12; May 11-23; Jun 6
  - Duplicate broadcasts, 1957; 3 folders (Box 251)
    Dates: Aug 22-28; Oct 31; Nov 12-15
  - Duplicate broadcasts, 1958; 2 folders (Box 251)
    Dates: Jan 1-30; Feb 4-27
  - Duplicate broadcasts, 1958; 6 folders (Box 252)
    Dates: Mar 6-7; Mar 10-31; Apr 2-8; Apr 9-18; May 7-8
  - Duplicate broadcasts, undated; 2 folders (Box 252)
- Part II. Congressional Record
  See also Part II, Published material: Congressional Record.
  - Congressional Record, 1963 Nov 27-1964 Sep 3 (Box 253)
  - Congressional Record, 1965 Feb 15-Mar 6; 5 volumes (Box 253)
  - Congressional Record, 1965 Mar 8-23; 5 volumes (Box 254)
  - Congressional Record, 1966 Feb 8 (Box 254)
- Part II. Miscellaneous
  - Books signed by author
    - Aleckson - Eyre (Box 255)
    - Farley - Kershner (Box 256)
    - King - Mueller (Box 257)
    - Neuhausler - Wood (Box 258)
  - Books of Betsy Lewis, signed by author (Box 259)
  - Books of Mr. and Mrs. C.H. Hurstom, signed by author (Box 259)
  - "Top of the News" miscellany
    - Index, 1952-1959, on microfilm, 2 reels
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 Jan 3-Apr 8 (Box 260)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 Sep 27-Dec 17 (Box 260)
    - Index, Jun 29-Dec 25 1964 (Box 260)
    - Biannual Index, Dec 30, 1963-Jun 26, 1964 (Box 260)
    - Biannual Index, Jul 1-Dec 27, 1963 (Box 260)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962 Dec 31-1963 Mar 8 (Box 260)
    - Miscellaneous, Oct 16, 1961-Dec 28, 1962 (Box 260)
  - Exclusive, Apr 8, 1962 (Box 260)